Andrew Strigaliov, Senior Software Developer

Warsaw, Poland, +48516395191, strigaliov4working@gmail.com

PROFILE

My whole career is related to tech startups. Most of them made or raised millions of USD. I have been through the entire software development cycle from scratch to enterprise multiple times. This experience and technical education allowed me to become a professional in Software Development. It helps me to clearly detect business goals, analyze the market, accurately estimate deadlines, effectively manage teams, and plan the future stages of product development.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Apr 2023 — Present

Senior Software Developer, Canvas Reply

Warsaw

- Worked on a large-scale project that is a group solution for an airline group headquartered in London.
- Implemented advanced Next.js middleware service to cache data and check the validity of it with polling interval resulting in a better UX and load time.
- Occasionally step in as a Team Lead for my team, consisting of fourteen people, including eight developers.

Nov 2019 — Apr 2023

Software Developer, ITechArt

Warsaw

- Implemented project addons for several services like Microsoft Teams, Google Calendar and Slack.
- Engineered and updated existed WebRTC protocol to work with different services.
- Created a roadmap for ITechArt Trainee Lab.
- Performed as a Team Lead for a Front-end team in Web3 domain.
- Created unique architecture pattern to support Smart Contract interactions with Front-end.
- · Participated in Big Data research for blockchain addresses in Ethereum, Polygon and Solana networks.

Sep 2019 - Nov 2019

Fullstack Trainee, ITechArt

Minsk

- Implemented five different pet-projects covering different topics and expertise.
- Learned Typescript and Nest.js as extra achievements.

EDUCATION

Sep 2016 — Jun 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc), Belarusian State

University

Minsk

SKILLS	MongoDB	Expert	Databases	Expert
	HTML & CSS	Expert	AWS	Expert
	JavaScript/Typescript	Expert	Vue.js	Expert
	React.js	Expert	Next.js	Expert
	Node.js	Expert	Fastify.js	Expert
	Nest.js	Expert	Nuxt	Expert
	GraphQL	Expert	Jest	Expert
	REST API	Expert	Solidity	Skillful

COURSES

Jan 2019 — Jun 2019

Rolling Scopes School, Software Development

LANGUAGES	English	C1	Belarusian	Native speaker
	Russian	Native speaker		

REFERENCES